<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<entries>

	<entry date="1/1/1988">
		<text>"Free Day"</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/2/1988">
		<text>"Looked with Reeds and Hartingers H. Liked Stogsdill Contacted Paul Work"</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/3/1988">
		<text>"Looked w Paul 12:30 - 2:00 Showed 4"</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/4/1988">
		<text>"Contacted Mrs. Reed. Coming Tues. 3:00 Looked w Paul again. Had to drop to $35,000 range. LIked Stogsdill. Gone to get his wife."</text>
	</entry>	

	<entry date="1/5/1988">
		<text>"Mrs. Reed 10:00 P.M. Showed several she liked. Kinda narrowed them down to: Scenic, Inmans + Hutchison ($59,900) St. James; D'Asto, Stevens"</text>
	</entry>		

	<entry date="1/6/1988">
		<text>"Got call from Thelma Walker - Inquiring of Zulligs for Beauty Shop - 12:00"</text>
	</entry>	

	<entry date="1/7/1988">
		<text>"Earl Wilson (573) 364-2897 Call Greg Call Harginers tonight 12:00 Luncheon for Hartlings Talked to Minnie Bradford. Might get Darrell to look at Williams Rd. Sat. Caribe - $600-900 per wk. Santibel Island Ft. Myers Beach - chamber of comm. (813)-463-6451. Holiday Inn 1-800-465-4329-115+6-115(2) Beach Best Western  - Ft. Myers Beach 1-800-528-1234 Around $200 for 5 Mld. Listings to Darrell Bradford. 2 - so brook - Williams Rd. + Coelbrook"</text>
	</entry>	

	<entry date="1/8/1988">
		<text>Hope Greg can come home - Call him Thurs. Talked to George Hartinger. He said to wait till next Sat. till I had more to show Might show Green Acres. Betty Feeler - Rt. 3 Box 3169 Need to call Bradfords to see Wms Rd. Janet Pearson - Cld her. She thinks he made an offer on something.</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/9/1988">
		<text>Mrs. Reed coming back, weather permitting - 9:00 See one in St. James Paul Work to be back in town. Hope he works w me. He already made offer on Redbud Lane. Showed Mrs. Reed: Bartlow, Inman, St. James, Daves, Reach, Hutchison, Elsie Cantrell Cld Give her some attention</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/10/1988">
		<text>""</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/11/1988">
		<text>"Need to call Heartlings for lunch. (573) 581-1363."</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/12/1988">
		<text>"Show: St. James new listing. Murry Lane. 174 Denny Ct $44,900 Kent Lane $44,900 Get in touch w Brenda Mahoney to see if I can get a showing. Yes, I can sell it her husband says, but not sure when she'll be ready."</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/13/1988">
		<text>"Tentative appoint Reed to see: Denny Ct. Kent Lane, Murry Lane + St. James Lunch w Mary - Chet Bredna's one time listing today for Mrs. Reed and pray"</text>
	</entry>	

	<entry date="1/14/1988">
		<text>"Talked to Bobby OH. Will give me 1-time showing. (573) 364-8866. 12:30 Lunch with Haertlings Call David Minichon 902 Murry Lane + 1321 Woodlawn and Oakmont. Appreciated it. Mrs. Reed to be here at 9:00 to see Kenty Lane, Murry Lane, Denny Ct. Brendas and possibly St. James. Get something ready for Elsie and Hartingers"</text>
	</entry>	

	<entry date="1/15/1988">
		<text>"Contacted Mr. Morris on Teodoro's lot. Not selling now be he will take it. Gave Elsie 10 hourses for possibilities to see Sat. (1) Maxwell (2) Scenic (3) College Hills (4) Aintree (5) Adrian (6) Inmans (7) Coventry (8) Old Eng (9) Kent Lane (10) Denny Ct. Lannie Harris - Cld. needs to find a palce to build (573) 249-4415. Make appmts for Sat for Cantrell, Reed + Harginer. Cld Emma on Rolla St. about her relatives. May be int. soon. (Wilsons) Need to talk to Henrdisens about decision on buying English's + maybe show to Mrs. Reed. Kenneth Morris P.O. Box 538 Camdenton 65020"</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/16/1988">
		<text>"Hartingers to see: Elmwood. So brook + 44 Rolla Gardens. 11:30 Olive St. $31,900 Elsie to go at 9:30. See: (1) Maxwell OPEN (2) S. Coll Hills (5) Adrian C-21 8:45 Mrs. Reed: to see Denny Ct., Kent Lane + Brednas 9:00 plus Whitney Lane + Orchard Hills"</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/17/1988">
		<text>""</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/18/1988">
		<text>"Vid-Call (573) 364-5668. Jill: 925 So St. Timbers Apt 301A SPringfield, MO 65806. Darrell Bradford (573) 368-8101. Call Carol Walraven (573) 729-6094 - Liked Wrights. Call Lana Johnson: (573) 364-4226. Keep in touch w Darrell Bradford."</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/19/1988">
		<text>"Dorothy Stimpson - (573) 364-2783 Inquiry on Steeplechase - Becky showed it today too. Cld Mr. Baily for 1-time showing. Doesn't think so will try to think of one."</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/20/1988">
		<text>""</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/21/1988">
		<text>"Tomahawk - (573) 374-8791 (573) 674-2440 To show: Jones to Mrs. Veght (573) 762-2721 4:00 P.M. Meet her at the house. Note from Carrotte's Elsie: to look at Houston Rd. $34,000 May keep hers. Fine w me. HA! Tried to call Brenda Mahoney to let her relax Call: hartingers"</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/22/1988">
		<text>"Jerry cld. Wish I could find location for him. business Contacted MRs. Ed Sexton - Salem, MO (573) 729-4463. Might follow up w note YES Interested but haven't decided on ocming to Rolla yet. Gerald Beyers Rt 2 - Box 238 Rolla (573) 762-2871. Talked to Mrs. Byers - (573) 762-2871. Likes Campbells, husabnd likes beset. Has listed w Stoltz"</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/23/1988">
		<text>"Reed (573) 674-2440"</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/24/1988">
		<text>"Janice Hartinger came to me. Not ignoring me she said. Busy . Bom"</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/25/1988">
		<text>"Talked to: DarrelBradford. Did drive by + will look soon. Can't arrange a time yet. This wk busy."</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/26/1988">
		<text>"Call: Greg Show: Mrs. Reed. 9:00 A.M. App Patels, Carols, Larry Browns $53,900 + Whitney. Key Drie by: Curtis Dr. Cld to confirm. Mrs. Reed has "sniffles" postponed till Sat. Talked to Twila - stil llikes Hensleys Reduced to: $63,900 - $33,500 - Net $29,000 Listed: Wiley Acres again $84,900 7A - $105,000 40 A"</text>
	</entry>

	<entry date="1/27/1988">
		<text>"Anniversary - 31st. Good time w kids. Lovely trip at Capital Plaza Write to:
			Paul Worstel. Looking for 3 - 10 A 1326 Martin Ct. Grapevine, TX 76051 Debbie Klaus (573) 364-5913 Looking for investment Ray Rheener - Cld on Alberts (573) 364-2488. Call back when they've finished decorating."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="1/28/1988">
			<text>"Cld Elsie. Thinking about moving to St. Louis now wants appraisal next wk. SHowed: Mr. Paulson: Mary Williams. Get back w info. Defniitely going to buy this year. Need a big place for 28 people, 14 little kids when they're together. Going to try to show them Emeleas."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="1/29/1988">
			<text>"Need to call Susan on Polings. Marily can't get a 1-time listing Looking for something for Byers - Wanda Ray. Cld on Danings - Just getting ideas - not ready to look $62,000"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="1/30/1988">
			<text>"Mrs. Reed 9:30 - to see: 2 on Whitney, Ft. Wyman, 2 on 9th St. Hope she buys Carols. Gerald Byers cld early A.M. to look Show: at 1:30"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="1/31/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>		

		<entry date="2/1/1988">
			<text>"Capital - 9% 1% cup 1 RO 5 cap assumable 95% loans 8 3/4 - 1 yr RO 1% loan fee 1-6 years 95% 8 1/2 - 1% loan 1 yr R.O 2% t up to 90% Can be converted to a fixed rate - 13th 60 mo 15 yrs 9 3/4 fixed 10 1/8 30 yrs 1 1/2 pts Wrote: Mrs. Reed, Bradfords + Paulsons Talked to Mrs. Leimkiller on 1 time showing"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/2/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/3/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/4/1988">
			<text>"Good! Mrs. Paulson cld me. Still considering Williams will let me know. Told her to give me some notice 4:00 P.M. To talk w Mrs Leimkiller. Yes, got one time listing"</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="2/5/1988">
			<text>"Cld Darrell back on the package deal. Seems interested. 9:30 showed Mrs. Reed again; still considering 9th st. and likes Whitney Lande and #7 Curtis Dr. Mld info she asked. Cld Mrs. Simpson. Said to call back Monday."</text>
		</entry>		

		<entry date="2/6/1988">
			<text>"Wilsons cld. Said might look"</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="2/7/1988">
			<text>"Sure enough. Cld at 9:20 met them at 10:30. Showed several. Seemed to still like Winchester."</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="2/8/1988">
			<text>"Curtis $296.81 co tax Call Mrs. Simpson Monday Going to wait for warmer weather Showed: Wilsons again. Told me they'd rather work w me than Darlene. Said they'd like me to show Winchester + write them offer cause they felt I would work harder for them."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/9/1988">
			<text>"Cld Wilsons Mr. Wilson - 11:30 to see Winchester. Cld Mrs. Reed - Eliminated 9th St. Leaning toward Curtis or Winchester Got offer on Winchester from Wilsons of $55,000. Talked to Mrs Reed again - About acreage behind Curtis Sounds better Talked to Mae Leimkiller. May list with me the end of Feb. (after her surgery) May also build some spec homes and let us list. Show: Darrell Bradford 5:15 the rental homes"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/10/1988">
			<text>"9:00 - Henricksens to v Carols house Call Mrs. Poulson - Still into in Williams. Call Hartingers - Got Wilsons together at $58,000 - Finallized"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/11/1988">
			<text>"Call Lana Johnson to tell her Maxwell will owner finance Wrote Wilsons Cld. Emma - Talked to: Minnie Bradford. Answered all questions."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/12/1988">
			<text>"Call: Greg Got call from Mark Smith on acreage (573) 341-2092 WHen I cld back w info he had given wrong number"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/13/1988">
			<text>"Kevins b-day Showed: Poulsons, Cedar Grove again. About to decide there's too much work. Got Larry Browns together."</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="2/14/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="2/15/1988">
			<text>"Wrote to: Joyce Grotenhairs - 14505 Tomasha, Indep. 64055 (816) 373-8456 Had holiday off"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/16/1988">
			<text>"Call: Lana Johnson. Yes. Will look on Sat, in a couple of wks Showed Darrell Bradford not going to buy Polings. Look for $25,000 range. To show Paulsons - 5:30 Emeleas - + Pattersons Talked to Earnie Cole - May hire Christ Beyke - will let me know."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/17/1988">
			<text>"Showed: Paulsons: Emeleas + Pattersons Go check Wests Drove by Hutchinson - $49,500 Lost Franks listing to Gleara Mace Hall Wrote to: Wayne Vanduser soliciting listing in Greenlefe Box 272. Rt 4. (573) 364-0754."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/18/1988">
			<text>"(573) 364-8181. Car serviced. To show Joyce, Olive St. 5:15 Key at C-21 Jack Wilson. (573) 225-6163 cld hadn't rec'd my letter yet. Seemed happy with their decision."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/19/1988">
			<text>"9:30 Dr. Thessing Marilyn unhappy on 1-time listing with Pattersons Call from Darlene. Seemed to take it O.k. on Wilsons I hope she believes me. It's imp. to me."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/20/1988">
			<text>"Call on Carron acreage Call from man in Heritage on upper priced home Joyce cld. Grotenhurs - talked to husband"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/21/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/22/1988">
			<text>"Wrote Paulsons w info, etc."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/23/1988">
			<text>"Mrs. Reed 11:30 to City Engineer. She cancelled. Eliminated the house. Had 2 new listings to show her - only saw 9th st. and again she thinks she likes it. Wants to see it Sat. 5:30  - Showed Bradfords 4 homes. Liked King Dr. Not ready for offer. Movz slow."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/24/1988">
			<text>"Mrs. Paulson - Fell in Hospital told her I'd contact next week."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/25/1988">
			<text>"Hopefully I'm gone to Florida"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/26/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/27/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/28/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="2/29/1988">
			<text>"Florida"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/1/1988">
			<text>"Florida"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/2/1988">
			<text>"Florida"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/3/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/4/1988">
			<text>"Back to work maybe. 30 mi East of Tampa"</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="3/5/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>		

		<entry date="3/6/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="3/7/1988">
			<text>"Cld: Mae Leimkiller - May list soon Cld Mrs. Wilson - Going to call her Realtor - see if they have loan comm. Cld: Mrs. Reed. Will be in Thurs 9:00 A.M. Talked to Karen Laramore - still thinking about Hawthorne Mld. Contracts to Wests."</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="3/8/1988">
			<text>"Cld Eybergs on lots. Wil send copy Mae Cld, Can take her drapes Rg, Refrig, sheers, rods and price it for $61,000 + 3%. Tried to get her to list but not ready. Cld: Realtor in St. Louis on Wilsons sale to see if loan had been approved. Talked to Broken. Will call back."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/9/1988">
			<text>"Show: Darrell - Bill Ave. $29,500 5:30 Get Key New A-frame roof put in 2 yrs ago - well ventilated furnace working last time renters lived there."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/10/1988">
			<text>"Showed Mrs. Reed once again. Didn't let her get to me today. Showed #58 Green Acres, Viburnam $48,000, Hillview $44,500. Drove by Hwy 72 and she liked Clayton in Coll. Hills. Txas for 1987 $255.72 + 55.17 El avg. per mo Reed - 9:00. Talked to Minnie Bradford - Very int. int Bill Ave. Gave info to her."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/11/1988">
			<text>"Talked to Jeanette Crosby about lots. She likes trees. Said I could go ahead + check on lots in Heritage. Tried to call Mel Marshall - Will in this P.M. Showed Mrs. Ketterer 63 North 3rd and Olive St. $36,000 (Nice) has to sell home 1st. Will get back to me."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/12/1988">
			<text>"10 A.M. Reed to see Wrights again. maybe yes + made offer (Hallelujah!) She cld the entire office. WOuld only go $55,000 but raised fofer to $57,000. Final offer. Their last counter $60,500"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/13/1988">
			<text>"Showed Darrell Bradford Bill Ave. Looked at Bill for 1 1/2 HRS. Finally got offer."</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="3/14/1988">
			<text>"Fryers on 7th St. (573) 364-1780 Call Thurs. perhaps to see Mae's on Whitney. Send info to Lisa Tiber. (573) 341-3179 Got it all ready to take by. C-21 Millie Weber (573) 391-6424 Wilsons - (573) 225-6163) Spent half the day talking to St. Louis on Wilsons. Committment on or before the 25th."</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="3/15/1988">
			<text>"Talked to Lisa Tilor (573) 341-3179. 1318 Truman - Apt 19. Send info on Homes for 3 girls. $40 - 45,000. Might look Sat at a few. Rejected Darrells offer. Darnell really disappointed. Mrs. Reed Rejected counter - still $3,500 apart. Showed Fryers."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/16/1988">
			<text>"David Hoss - 138 Woodcrest (573) 364-3090 Cancel David - Working with Boone Prock. Talked to Mel Marshall about a reduction. WIll talk to Dic. Talked to Hensleys about a reduction and a sign (yes) Talked to Larry about Bradfords coming in + Laramores. Mrs. Reed in. Bought a F330. Didn't go thru."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/17/1988">
			<text>"Call Mr. Fryer - Call Mae Call Mr. Fryer yes, I did. Fryers to look in 50's - might call or send her something things to drive by. Closing on Larrys - Sigler. 1:00 P.M. - Thank goodness. Checked into the Gooch property. Was told to avoid it. Told Karen. Look for others closing."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/18/1988">
			<text>"Talked to Mrs. Ketterer. Still likes Horters Needs to sell theirs 1st. Roof 8 yrs old Horters. Talked to Karen after sending her some info on homes. Wants to see #7 Curtis at 4:30."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/19/1988">
			<text>"Shirley's b-day. 2:00 to show Lisa Tiber and parents. 4:30 to see Horters - Marta Van Treese (573) 341-2738. Cancelled for today. Tom Laramore was in, wrote offer on Curtis Dr. James gone to Lebanon."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/20/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/21/1988">
			<text>"Got $57,900 counter offer on Curtis for Laramores. Sub 60's - maybe newer - on Tiebers. No farther than Forum from U.M.R. 2521 Pepermil Lake Ct. Chesterfield Mo 63017 (573) 532-6090. Heard from Mr. Friar - still looks like Aintree. Doesn't want to see others right now. Ml'd info 3-21. Scout for them. 5:30 Show Darrell Bradford Hwy Y $16,000 Fm A. Liddie Demay (573) 394-3558 or (573) 225-4474 Cld Liddie. Assured me closing on Wilsons would be the 31st."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/22/1988">
			<text>"Reduced Irwins to $59,900. Lot 41, 43, 44, 45, 46 COventry. Got offer from Darrell on FM 4A. Fryars decided on #43 in Steeplecahse. Kenny to get bid ready by Sat. Maybe. Sold Kennys home in Ponzer. My listing."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/23/1988">
			<text>"Get listing today on Ayers. 3:30 on Rolla St. Road. 2 Bdrm with 3 room house behind. Listed for $42,900. Cld Columbus Craft - (417) 256-9022. Needs rental at this point."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/24/1988">
			<text>"11:00 To list Peggy Wiggins - 4 yr old home Elk Prairie, 2nd home. 6 miles out 2 story - 5 bdrm 5 Acres wooded, fenced (573) 341-3863 Got approval on Wilsons home in St. Louis to close Mar. 31st. Proceed with their sale. Probably be Mon. morn."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/25/1988">
			<text>"Mrs. Worsizwicz Dayton Ohio. Lois Cochrans daughter - Under $100,000 4 Bdrm 2 baths - double garage Be in Monday. Got Mrs. Wiggins listing. Great Talked to Karen Laramore"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/26/1988">
			<text>"Mr. Roemer Cld. Showed him Marie's at 4:00 Sun"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/27/1988">
			<text>"Greg's b-day. Cld Greg Didn't get to see him on his b-day."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/28/1988">
			<text>"Sent Rosemer's info on Maries. Fluents $54,900. Lee Waits in like gangbusters to talk about listing 10. Shirley + I to split listing. Lois Cochran - May come today - show campbells Laramores? Harvest Fields, Hogans, Burgher. Co. Sidz Sycamore $79,900 Line Barnitz $89,900 Whitney Lane? $93,300"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/29/1988">
			<text>"Gone to Joe's Funeral"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/30/1988">
			<text>"10:00 A.M. To list Lee Waits, Sue went for us. Did well she said. Showed Wokizwicz all day. Felt like I earned their confience, trust and loyalty. Not positive they are coming to Rolla. Send material periodically."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="3/31/1988">
			<text>"Cld Owsley on lots in Heritage will call back so I can contact Jeaneth Stan and Carol Waskizwicz. 3912 Meadowsweet Dr. Dayton, Ohio (454) 24-4807 (513) 236-2412 Cld. Karen. Suggested she drive by Williams - Cedar Grove - Got Mr. Fryers deal all together. Listed adn contrac signed on teh build job. Cld Karen Laramore."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/1/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Minnie about the one on 7th. Will drive by. Wrote: Jeanette Miller on Lots in Heritage Got call on DeIberos - Howard Smith - neighbors"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/2/1988">
			<text>"Celebrate Birthdays!"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/3/1988">
			<text>"Celebrate Birthdays!"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/4/1988">
			<text>"11:00 Show: WhitneySchneiders. Tiebers Did show! 2. on 9th, Bill Ave., Elmwood, Scenic, WHitney, Hillview, Will be back next week. 1513 Scenic 1:00 - 1:10 Erdman"</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="4/5/1988">
			<text>"Got all invitations out. Beauty shop."</text>
		</entry>		

		<entry date="4/6/1988">
			<text>"Showed Karen Laramore - Cedar Grove. LIkes it a lot but worried about all the work. Rec'd $4,000 upon completion of foundation from Freyers. Asked about faucetts, cut off, TV receptacles and adding bldg. TOld him he would have to decide by Fri."</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="4/7/1988">
			<text>"Bob Link. Kinda slow today. Decateur Ill Civic Center $26,500 Lori 4424 Mr. Harrison Williams was in - not really to list but wanted ust oknow his is available at 506 E. 13th $30,000 Net, steel siding, cent Aiy 1,"</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="4/8/1988">
			<text>"Kinda slow today. Been down to see Kenny Campbell - Home will soon be under roof and another paymt due. Doors will be in today. Need to pick up Key + cleaning. Wrote Waskizwicz again."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/9/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/10/1988">
			<text>"Ed. Courses at Rolla Inn 9 - 12"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/11/1988">
			<text>"Lisa Tirper (573) 341-3179 Ed. Courses - Rolla Inn 1-4. Got anothe rpayment from Fryers. Dep. today. Given to 1 Church luncheon Nice - Sycamore (573) 364-1731 (573) 364-3506. Talked to LIsa Tieber. Folks will call. May come later in the week."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/12/1988">
			<text>"Completed Ed. Courses for license renewal. Going to Gregs maybe 7:25 dinner Cled for Tiebers, not home. Cld Lisa. Vick: Thomas Cld. on land again for parents. FmHA accepted original offer on Hwy Y. Bradofrds lost out. Tried for"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/13/1988">
			<text>"12:00 Lunch with Loretta 1:00 Meet with Lori 2:00 Beauty Shop 5:00 Sparlins FmHA buyers 5:30 Heasleys - Presented offer on their home. Accepted subj. to Financing"</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="4/14/1988">
			<text>"FmHA = Int Credit $17,850 FmHA. reg $23,350 max 4:30 Ben and Lisa Spurlin - To see 7th Street. Need to sell trailer 1st. Liked both homes: Fryers and Davis. Will talk to FmHA DeVries 3187 Contacted chuck on floor covering for Fryers."</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="4/15/1988">
			<text>"$5,000 pd. to Kenny Campbell Need to collect from Fryers Check will be delivered mon at 8:30. Tried to call Tiebers - Looking like the week-end that parents may be coming. Bad news for me. Tried to call Geo. Hartinger to tell them about Fryers. Yes and he's interested at least."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/16/1988">
			<text>"Tiebers not coming till next Sunday. Thank goodness. Tied up this week-end."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/17/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/18/1988">
			<text>"9:00 To Campbells to take Check. not home. 1-:00 Mon Fryers to Hausners for carpet choosing + tile. Talked to John Hall about Maries. Driving by he said. Cld. Karen Laramore Kind of discouraged in a nice way looking at just anything till home sells."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/19/1988">
			<text>"Talked to Jackie Ayers - Took check to Kenny and letter from Douglas couple 3:00 to list - Olivers. Write Tiebers - Chamber of Commerce Banquet 7:30 Spurlins - Have to wait till FmHA approves them."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/20/1988">
			<text>"Talked to 11:30 West Cruise - Wiggins Closing if we get power of Attorney from Germany 1:15 Beauty Shop 3:00 to list Olivers - yes"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/21/1988">
			<text>"Closing on West/Cruise. 1397 Centerre and Capital 30 days. (573) 364-7471 Need to pick up Fryers last payment before closing. Fryers will owe for 3 loads of dirt. Have chosen the plush carpet like the Hi-lo on Aintree + have selected tile. Wrote to Dorrothy's + Laramores. Need to contact Jim Hood's sister: McGinnis for 1st time  homeuyers. Yes. Got a good reception. Told her about Fryers + Olivers. Said she was anxious to look."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/22/1988">
			<text>"Talked to Mae Leimkiller. Will proably list within a couple of weeks. Asked about 4 Playes. Found out about Eyurgs new units. Sounds great! 1,000 sq. ft units - 2 Bdrm. garage. Radiant floor heat. Beautiful grounds. Great location. Great looking! (609) 893-2273 Need to get sign on olivers + take picture. Call: Chuck + Dorothy Neas - #90 Magnolia St. Browns Mills, N.J. 08015 Call Mrs. Ginnis Lisa Spurlin Cld again."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/23/1988">
			<text>"Mavis Costiglion - Realtor (609) 853-5311 893-3498 September 20th"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/24/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/25/1988">
			<text>"Fryer 364-8140 next wk. To show Laramores at 1:00 1-Vida-2 on Elk Prairie, Dry by McCutcheon. Referred by Mel Willaims. Carol Whipperford Wipperfurth (573) 341-0956 200 Acres of land between Edgar and Anutt 100,000 0 - Co. Rd 22 3 bdrm ranch 1700 - 1 1/2 + 1/2 Listed at 20,000"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/26/1988">
			<text>"6:00 - to Annett - to list Farm Linda Webster - Cld. for FmHA home. Cl'd on Inmons + Kearol. Spurlins to see several 4:00 P.M. Still like FmHA home of Davis - 1:30 Beauty Shop - 4:00 P.M. Sparlins to see No. Wye - Lakeside Estates, 807 Ridgeview 29,000 + Ayers $42,900"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/27/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/28/1988">
			<text>"364-8740 - Fryer Donna Lane Cld 364-2393 Looking for small tract to build in Doolittle area Found on Sugar Tree. TOld her about 2A tracts So on to Int 11:00 Thurs... Jim Brasure - cancelled 2:30 Linda Webster TO look at: 3 homes today 762-3209 Going FmHA. Using mother's income Eligible for int. credit - eligible for existing home of their specs, inventory home or bldg new one. 1,300 sq. ft."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/29/1988">
			<text>"1:30 P.M. Beauty Shoppe Talked to: Mrs. Tieber - Not coming Sun. Asked about 9th Street."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="4/30/1988">
			<text>"To list Hollands at $61,900 hopefully Showed: Mr. Kidwell (573) 341-4241 Got note from Corrots Will be up in May"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/1/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/2/1988">
			<text>"Mr. Kidwell cld. Not int in Jones - (573) 341-4241 Asked about the 2A. 10:30 LInda Webster To see D'Asto, Wakefield, Fox Creek + Inman. Kathleen Cld.  - Will be looking for Mabel, looks like next week."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/3/1988">
			<text>"Steven Stacy - Cld on Earth shuttered homes. David Minich - not going to sell."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/4/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Mae Leimkiller - NOt ready to list yet. Cld. Mr. Kidwell - on C-21 listing at Doolittle Cld. Hensleys to make sketch for Elaine. Cathy + Ron Frank from MA Willbein May 13 to look 35-40,000 Cld. Mrs. Paulson - Need to send her some things. Talked to Lisa Spurlin - Need to be out of trailer by May 31st. Might have to rent temporarily."</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="5/5/1988">
			<text>"MHDC - 1st Time 8 3/4 2 _ 1 3% down 41,400 Max. Lisa Surplin 265-8744 Lisa Tieber 1:15 To see 10th St. + Fox Creek Folks won't be here Sunday. Cld. Mrs. Fryer about the doors. $57,900."</text>
		</entry>		

		<entry date="5/6/1988">
			<text>"Tried to call Fue-Wen Liou (573) 364-1503 Already working with C-21. Jerry Tennyson. 5:00 P.M. Lisa Tieber to see Franklins + Fox Creek"</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="5/7/1988">
			<text>"Good day with Greg"</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="5/8/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/9/1988">
			<text>"Got call from Mrs. Light (573) 341-3636 on 18th and Cedar. Home is sold. Corrottos to look Saw: Herrmans, Irwins Drove by Greentrees, Maes."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/10/1988">
			<text>"Mabel + Kathleen to start looking. Going to wait a while. Need to call Jerry Tennyson. Need to scout for Corrottos."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/11/1988">
			<text>"Corrottos 10:00 to Leimkillers, maybe show: Franklins on 10th St. ? Show #7 South Murry."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/12/1988">
			<text>"Cld LIsa Tieber. Will talk more to her folks Sat. about 10th St. 2:00 P.M. Franks 35-40,000. Showing: Davis, Inmans, Meeks, Old. Eng. 2 on Rolla St. Ron + Cathy Frank - 6037 Wild Ginger Ct. 301-740-2259 Work 301-964-6222 Columbia, MD 21044. Looking $35-40,000 range. Cld. Ann Webster - Glad I cld'd. Should have cld earlier. Need to scout for Franks. Need to scout for Webers - Maybe send Mr. Light literature on 7th St. maybe."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/13/1988">
			<text>"Wendell O'Grosky Cld. back. Doesn't think he's int in the 4 plex location. 9:00 A.M. Showed: many more today to Frank. Narrowed it down to 2 1st choice: #7 South Murry - Sold before we coudl even see it twice. Went to 2nd choice - Met here at 10:00. Went over contract till 11:30. Made offer Sat. morn Got together."</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="5/14/1988">
			<text>"Frank here at 8:30. Got 500 Fox Creek sold to Franks. WEnt back to look. Feeling good about it."</text>
		</entry>	

		<entry date="5/15/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/16/1988">
			<text>"Talked to: Gloria Huskey. Might be ready to sel trailer w 3.4 Acres and start looking. Send things today or tomorrow. Yes I did. Talked to Mrs. McGinnis. Doesn't really have the amount for down payment and closing costs. Will talk to husband. Asked her to go look at Fryers. Franks  to lunch at Brunos."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/17/1988">
			<text>"Need to send Poulsons material. Vyes talked to Lisa Spurlin. Got Mae Leimkiller listing - $67,500. Wrote to Waskiwicz. Went Bradfords info."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/18/1988">
			<text>"Gone to Springfield."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/19/1988">
			<text>"Wrote Lisa Spurlin."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/20/1988">
			<text>"Made some random calls on getting listings on Highland (1) Robert Rahner. Said to try him next year. His son is graduating (2) Talked to Betsy Hansen - Might know aneighbor, can't tell me yet. Will call me. (3) Cld. Stan Marshall (573) 364-2796 (4) Left message on Keith Rickerts. rec. (5) Cld. Marjorie Doyle New in neighborhood (6) Wilbert Burton - Not home. (7) Harlan Nelson at work (573) 341-2252 (8) Leland Perry (573) 341-3590 (9) Geo. Bell 364-3927 (10June Harper - left message (11) Raymond Fox"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/21/1988">
			<text>"Bobby Ott cld."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/22/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/23/1988">
			<text>"$54,900 1400 Highland Brk.Frame Gloria Husky Cld (Here we go again) Wanted to see 4. Luebberts, English, Scenic, Prestons, Highlands. Lisa Spurlin Cld. Wants to see 2 Gone to Greg's - good time."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/24/1988">
			<text>"Gone to Gregs"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/25/1988">
			<text>"Bdauty Shop - 12:30"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/26/1988">
			<text>"Showed G. Huskey 10-11:00 - Tosco Highlands. Luebberts Forum Dr. Scenic + Ft. Wyman (appmt) 50 Laird. Like Corbins + English. Mae L. cld. last night. Cld. Spurlins (about ready) Will call next wk. Cld. Lisa Tieber - Parents are talking. Maybe be down next week."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/27/1988">
			<text>"Call on Zulligs."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/28/1988">
			<text>"11:00 Bill Cornell to see Gentrys."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/29/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/30/1988">
			<text>"Beth's b-day Hectic but turned out good. Greg got to come after all."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="5/31/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Cathy Frank - Cld. Minnie Bradford. About Olivers + Ozark. Cld. Gloria Hyskey Brenda Mahoney Cld. Going to list with me around the 15th. Cld. Lisa Spurlin Mr. Biols Cld. Wants to see Gentrys at 3:00 Liked it pretty good. May show his wife."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/1/1988">
			<text>"Call Mike Bell about appraisal if Stoltz hasn't made contact."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/2/1988">
			<text>"Rt. 1 Box 35 Feeler Lisa Surlin Cld. Going to drive by Sally Rd. then maybe make offeron Old Eng. Fri."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/3/1988">
			<text>"Lisa Spurlin - 4:30 - 5:00 $42,500 To see Sally Rd. home. Cld. Hensleys on closing info. 1:15 Beauty SHop. 1311 Forum Drive. Note from Stan Waskiewicz w resume"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/4/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/5/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/6/1988">
			<text>"1311 Forum Drive Cld. Lisa Spurlin - Cld. Gloria Huskey. In Bible school. Will look next week. Cld. Fryers to see what they're thinking about moving or extending. Allison reffered Bill Wietes to me Rt. 4 - Box 93"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/7/1988">
			<text>"Call or write Tiebers Cld. Bill Cornell. Couldn't tell me much."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/8/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Spurlins this morning. Think they're going to wait. Think they've spent some of their money. Had walk-in Mrs Gerri Sharp + Mother - Looked at Blanche's + Mae L. LIked BLanc's I think hope to hear soon."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/9/1988">
			<text>"Need to call Biols: 341.4865 Tried! Wrote: Chuck + Nease"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/10/1988">
			<text>"Hensley CLosing 9:30 yes Need to get back to them today or Mon."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/11/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/12/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/13/1988">
			<text>"Call Gloria Huskey - Tried to call Cld. Brenda Mahoney - Ready to list end of w. , she hopes 6435 NW Compass Greg 536-0604 Got good call from Pam Horton"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/14/1988">
			<text>"Hensley Closing Mtg. on disclosure farm which is effective July 1"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/15/1988">
			<text>"Fryer Closing - 1:30 tentatively"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/16/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/17/1988">
			<text>"Moving Day"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/18/1988">
			<text>"Good time with Fathers"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/19/1988">
			<text>"Good time with Greg"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/20/1988">
			<text>"Out of town 1311 Forum"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/21/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Sharps today. Mother has been ill but decided against Irwin home because of the 2 bdrms. Offered to show her more. Mae Leimkiller cld + cancelled her listing 5:00 To List Mahoneys Call from Near's friends. They're coming the 2nd of July. Want to buy quick. Need something quick."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/22/1988">
			<text>"To show: 4:30 - Huskeys Meet here Showed Orchard Hills + Ridgeview."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/23/1988">
			<text>"On duty 11:30 - 2:30 4:00 to show Spurlins: Belmont GOt offer on Belmont from Spurlins. Letter from Stan Waskiewicz"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/24/1988">
			<text>"Retha Brekmacher 435-9285 Talked to GLoria. To list Fri."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/25/1988">
			<text>"Charley's b-day Got offer on 7th St. Good counter offer"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/26/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/27/1988">
			<text>"Lot 36. Brookridge Estates #3 78 x 105 mld. packet ot Hortons. Contact Geo. Holland at 4:00 P.M. today. Has 48 hrs. to go ahead + buy 7th St."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/28/1988">
			<text>"Lyle Champ - Coming in to list home on Coventry 3:00 - 4:00 P.M. 7:30 Titus to meet with Spurlins - "</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/29/1988">
			<text>"Work in A.M."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="6/30/1988">
			<text>"Aiken Louis Aitkien 5102 Queeny Tower Bldg Barnes Hosp. Plaza St. Louis 10:30 To show Gloria new one on Winchester Oak Hill, + Clayton Ct. 62,500 chg to Fri."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/1/1988">
			<text>"Gloria Husky to list mobile home. 10:00 A.M. then to look. Show husband later. Show: Oak Hill, Clayton Ct. and Winchester Show husband. English + Cordins 4:00 - 4:30"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/2/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/3/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/4/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/5/1988">
			<text>"Hortons coming in. Be ready! 6435 NW Compass Lawtwon, Okla. 73505 Also Chuck + Dorothy Neas will be in to buy. 10:00 A.M. Talked to them today. Showed about 8 places. Be back tomorrow"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/6/1988">
			<text>"Still showing"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/7/1988">
			<text>"Narrowed it down to 4 properties: Back to see them today: V Hwy,, Smith's on 72, English + Campbells. Got contract on V Hwy. ($48,500)"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/8/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Tiebers. Suppose to make offer on LIttle woods Sat. at 11:00. Spurlin - To see home again on Belmont 5:30."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/9/1988">
			<text>"9:30 Hollands to see 1003 w 9th St. 11:00 Tiebers to make offer on LIttlewoods. Yes 41,000 1:30. Going home to be with Greg the week. end."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/10/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/11/1988">
			<text>"Got counter on LIttlewoods. 45,000. Showed Tiebers 2 homes. LIked Rolla St. Rd. Coming back Tues. eve. to decide between the 2"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/12/1988">
			<text>"Dr. King - CLd. on Rentals Gave info on COll. Hills and Highland. Will get back Tiebers - 1:00 at the office See Littlewoods. then Rolla St. Rd. Make decision. Will call Wed."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/13/1988">
			<text>"Cld Tiebers Making counter - 43,500 on 9th St. Deliverd to CB. Cld Carrottos - Nice reception - Haven't sold home. Will keep in touch. Ask Titus about Spurlins. Will call me tomorrow."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/14/1988">
			<text>"Pre-Approval 10:00 To Vichy with this here's Jerry To see the store 1:30 Mike Jones Wnated my advice on what to do his home to see an increase in profit. Will list with me. SHould I contact Paulsons again? I doubt it. Hollands to see home in St. James again 5:30 and also Rolla St. 364-2416"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/15/1988">
			<text>"Folks Anniv Sue's b-day. Closing Frank/Bayers 10:00 Maxwell (573) 364-2416 Call: Gloria Huskey. IF free to look MEet w Tiebers - 10:00 To see Littlewoods"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/16/1988">
			<text>"Work"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/17/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/18/1988">
			<text>"(573) 364-7687 Cedar Grove 79,900 Call houses in for home tour CHuck Neas #90 Magnolia St., Browns Mills, N.J. 08015 Showed Mr adn Mrs. Clutch. From 10:30 - 4:30 Clutches cld. Want to see Renicks old home + Woodlawn + Roberts"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/19/1988">
			<text>"Wanted to see only LIberty + Renicks + Roberts Got offer on Renicks 99,500 on a 109,500 Waiting for answer Bad news: Counter full price. Buyers irritated + tired. GOne home. Left 2 blank contracts and blank check. Said I will hear from them soon."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/20/1988">
			<text>"SHowed Clutches the Eudaly home. Wrote to Clutches. Sent disclsure too Talked to Ron Calhoun on Tiebers. Close but he thinks we're O.K."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/21/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Gloria Huskey - No one showed on home tour. Apologized. Cld. Betty Soltz and complained. Contacted Jerry on Earnest deposit - tore up check. Wrote: George HOllands W E. Dep. Wrote: Dan Clutch. Cld. Sue Tieber."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/22/1988">
			<text>"Beauty Shop Not much going on today."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/23/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/24/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/25/1988">
			<text>"Mr. Clutch Cld. Asking about Gentry's. 646-3325. Need to hit it these 3 days. Have fun the weekend. Talked to Vicki Thomas - land for parents Need to sell AYers home. SHe called. They're getting deserate. May have to rent."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/26/1988">
			<text>"Lunch - Mary Ann Wrote: Clutch's Had termite inspection on 804 East 7th St. Cld Sue Tieber on."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/27/1988">
			<text>"Call Ron Back - Thinks we will get an approval soon on Tiebers. 1:15: To show Marrion Condo"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/28/1988">
			<text>"Going to Ava - Take off a few days, on to Branson"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/29/1988">
			<text>"Gone to Play 10:30 - "</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/30/1988">
			<text>"Gone to Play"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="7/31/1988">
			<text>"Great time Really fun!"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/1/1988">
			<text>"Franks - Coming - (573) 364-2416. Mrs. Maxwell Cld,. about getting together w Campbells"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/2/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/3/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/4/1988">
			<text>"Got note from Franks. Talked to Greg News not too good"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/5/1988">
			<text>"Wrote to: Chuck Neus Wrote to: Dan Clutch with a lot of info. 1:30 Beauty SHop Shirley Giesher - (573) 364-3488 Cld. Tickled she cld. Wants to look in 20's. Needs to list hers"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/6/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/7/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/8/1988">
			<text>"Carol Winters News better on Ratings. Feel better. Gredg feels better Talked to SHirley Giesler - not finding anything very good in the 20's. Will list right away."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/9/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/10/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/11/1988">
			<text>"(573) 364-7226 (57) 364-8500 Curdsttis"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/12/1988">
			<text>"Tentative Closing: Tieber/Littlewood 2:30 - United Chg'd to 9:00. Went well Cld. LIsa Spurlin. Cld Jackie Ayers - Will rent for 375"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/13/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/14/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/15/1988">
			<text>"Gone to Columbia"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/16/1988">
			<text>"Irene Spencer Cld. Thinking of selling REntal property will check back."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/17/1988">
			<text>"Got call from Mr. Nickason (573) 364-1212 (573) 341-3056 on honell's land."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/18/1988">
			<text>"6:00 P.M. Rodney to see 6th St. home. Becky's b-day lunch - 11:45 1:00 Meet Lori at my house Wrote Shirley Giesler. Harold Baker Cld. Referred by David Minch selling a home in Kansas. Will start looking Fri."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/19/1988">
			<text>"Harold Baker - To start looking in 40's. 5:00 Nice Man: Saw Champs, Ridenhours, Giddens, Morris, Koederitz + Redbud"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/20/1988">
			<text>"Sherry's b- day 10:00 - Harold Baker to look again - Showed 6 SHowed: Mahoneys, Burges, Ayers, Inman's, Orchard Hills. Drove by: Lacbberts"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/21/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/22/1988">
			<text>"OFFTODAY but worked"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/23/1988">
			<text>"9:30 staff mtg. 5:00 P.M. Mr. Baker to see: Haslags, 213 Steeplechase 1304 Broadway"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/24/1988">
			<text>"Cathy Frank - 11:45 lunch Mrs. Virgil Baker (Lois) Walk-in. Lives on Old. St. James"</text>
		</entry>


		<entry date="8/25/1988">
			<text>"Noon Luncheon for Lori Wrote: Clutch's sent Sept. magazine Showed: Shirley 5th St. and Ozark Will list Monday, she thinks. 1304 Broadway '72 fenced"</text>
		</entry>


		<entry date="8/26/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>


		<entry date="8/27/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>


		<entry date="8/28/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/29/1988">
			<text>"David Price (573) 341-3126"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/30/1988">
			<text>"Got 2 new hourses listed of Campbells on Coventry Got Norman Long's listed Need to get sign up."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="8/31/1988">
			<text>"Talked to: Mr. Clutch again. Will be coming the 17th. 5:00 to see 5 homes (Mr. Baker.) Gieslers 5:30 - Showed: Watson, Lewis (log) Crumps + Gieslers. Asked again about Mahoneys + Champs. Got Shirley Gieslers listed."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/1/1988">
			<text>"2:00 Elsie Cantrell to look at Koederitz and Adrian. Showed Campbells new ones. Cld. Sheryl back with answers."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/2/1988">
			<text>"10:00 Dr. Butts 11:30 To meet Elsie at Giddens + show Irwins."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/3/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/4/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/5/1988">
			<text>"Good time w Greg at Meadow Lake. Had 6 birdies (73) Talked him into coming down"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/6/1988">
			<text>""1:30 Dr. Barry Bass chg'd appmt. Hectic day 4:00 P.M. Wilson/DeIbero Closing 4:45 To show Mr. Baker Koederitz home. 7:45 Typed offer for Mr. Baker.</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/7/1988">
			<text>"Got offer together on Baker/Koederitz. Got call from Mr. Clutch. Said to make offer on Roberts. Property had just been reduced to 74,900. Countered with that. Mr. Clutch said forget it. Thought Roberts would reconsider but decided not to."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/8/1988">
			<text>"11:00 Mr. Baker to United. Will be appraised Tuesday. Grand Opening! Big turnout! Lots of my people came. 3:00 P.N. Elsie to see Irwins. Got packet in for Spurlins to Del. Mar. What a hassle. 6:30 Got offer from Elsie on Irwins."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/9/1988">
			<text>"Got Irwin deal together at $55,500 talked to Greg."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/10/1988">
			<text>"Closing on Spurlin/Miles went well - a little worried though. People seem happy."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/11/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/12/1988">
			<text>"And... its Mon. Again. Need to list Elsies. Talked to: Mrs. Neus. Will need a partial loan. Need to send application. Talked to Ron. Loan on Cantrells looks good. Will send application."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/13/1988">
			<text>"List Elsies at 3:00 P.M. 2:15 Consultation w Dr. Bass."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/14/1988">
			<text>"Beauty SHop 1:15 Look for Corrottos. Mr. CLutch popped in unexpectedly, not thrilled. Dropped everything. SHowed several will be back Mon."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/15/1988">
			<text>"(573) 364-3333 Rm. 11 Clutch SHirley Giesler Jackie Ayers 756-8534 9:30 - 9:45 Corrottos Thessings to look. SHowed 5 homes. Liked Hanks Got along well. Should call before they leave Wed. Dennis Perry (573) 364-0757 Cld. Looking w Jackie Got offer on Champs. Countered w 51,500. Picked up sign on Marhsalls - Put on Shirley's w arrow + Elsie."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/16/1988">
			<text>"Mr. Clutch coming at 9:00 A.M. Be ready! Cld. Will not be in today but the following week. Will let me know ahead. Talked to Neus' Realtors Broker. Assured me all is O.K. Appraisal is Sept. 20."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/17/1988">
			<text>"Mr. Clutch to be in Not coming until next week.""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/18/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/19/1988">
			<text>"Mon at 9:00 AM at Wiggins - Campbell -BUrton 9:00 A.M. Inspect Koederitz. Mr. Clutch to be back. Who knows when 10:00 Clutch's to look. Showed many, many homes 2 in St. James, Vienna Rd., 8th St. Jackie Wilson, Voights, Coll. Hills, Liberty."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/20/1988">
			<text>"Curtis. Made offer on Voights of 71,800 Counter of 75,000 was accepted. 8:30 Mr. Clutch was in. Finalized things. Loan approved. Beauty Shop."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/21/1988">
			<text>"Contacted Mrs. WIlson. Is going to list soon. Try to get out of town this eve. Going to Gregs. 1:30 to look with Mrs. Perry (573) 364-4694 45-$55,000. Show Kenny's new ones. Show Mahoneys for out of town. Point Bluff Rd., Orchard, Old English, Champs, Haslags, Mahoneys, Gieslers.Closed on mobile home for kids. Will look Fri."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/22/1988">
			<text>"Carol Whipperfurth 1343 Veek Rd. Stoughton, Wis 53559 (608) 873-5686 Steve Robinson 762-3275 $500 (602) 726-6977"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/23/1988">
			<text>"11:00 Tentative Closing on Buker/Koederitz. Yes. Maybe show: Ohers."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/24/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/25/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/26/1988">
			<text>"9:45 To show Corrottos. Hanks home again. Liked it real well. Insurance agent won't insure Voight home until Wood stove is replaced. Barb House will call them."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/27/1988">
			<text>"160 9:00 A.M. To show Mr. and Mrs. Parry 4 Bdrm. Showed 8 homes: Prestons, Fraziers, Woodlawn, Peachtree. Meadow Ct. Lewis', W 13th, Curtis Drive. May look again this wk. with husband. Tried to call Brenda Mahoney for extension of listing. Voight's to replace stove. Cl'd Clutch's They were happy."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/28/1988">
			<text>"9:00 A.M. Mrs. SPencer to be in to list rental property. Yes at 47,5000 Talked to Mrs. Wayman. Might sell. Will call. 509 E. 6th. Mike Maruzco - Mel Williams told him to call. Cld about log home. Has a home to sell on Hartville Rd. (573) 341-0928"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/29/1988">
			<text>"Kick Eng (573) 364-4054 Sears UL Bathroom. 10:00 To list Jack Wilson Split with Marily I guess. Chg'd to 4:30. 2:00 P.M. To list mobile home - Melissa Today - 63 South 2 mi. 2nd drive past Lewiws Garage Hold up on Appmt till he checks with Bank. Am. Fam $206 Cld. Nancy Thessing. Talked to Mr. Clutch. Wants heat turned on. Elect. Will be in his name. Mon Cld Barb."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="9/30/1988">
			<text>"Did well with Mrs. WIlson but will talk to son before she sets price. Really hurt by her comments but that's life. COuldn't have done differently. I don't htink. Wouldn't change anything. Dissapointed the way it was handled. Cld. Mrs. Sharp but no answer Cld. for Cherryl Getz (Gate) Got Cheryl and got good reception at Drury - Not in yet."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/1/1988">
			<text>"My birthday!"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/2/1988">
			<text>"Really Good weekendend. Everyone here to celebrate!"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/3/1988">
			<text>"Old. Mike Marzuno to confirm sale of log home. Look for similar one or combination. 11:00 A.M. - Kick Eng inspection on Irwins. 1:00 - Perm Gave Parrys Particulars - Not too big of a hurry 55,000 $2500 down. 50,000 with 3% down 3% down pts. 2. 10 1/27. Did call Mrs Wayrman. Got her daughter-in-law. Good reception - will let me know."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/4/1988">
			<text>"Tried to call Mrs. Orr. Did call Gloria Huskey - Seems O.K. but won't extend now. Will give one time listing if we have someone. Cld. Kenny Campbell last night to extend listing."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/5/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Elsie. She's going to trust me yet. Already had the inspection done when she cld. Cld. Mrs. Orr - Went by to see Lowell Campbell. His Kellhim for listing again."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/6/1988">
			<text>"(573) 364-6638 Bob Tyler Estill Sharps 759-6424 364-0610 - Baker P.O. Box 305 Edith Hensley surgery - send flowers Marsha Thomas Cld. on Wilson property. Talked to Mrs. Parry again. Seemed receptive. Tried to call Hensleys. Cld. Mr. Wayman again. Will decide this weekend. Pheasant Hill sold today my listing."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/7/1988">
			<text>"11:30 Cantrell/Elsie CLosing and Irwin Went well. Had renters in. Seem to want Ayers. Didn't come back."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/8/1988">
			<text>"10:00 A.M. To show Mrs. Simmons, the Wilson Home. Loved it Wants to make low offer."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/9/1988">
			<text>"Open House"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/10/1988">
			<text>"Jackie Glenn"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/11/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Mrs. Wilson on Winchester Likes home, doing O.K. Tried to call Bill Cornell. Yes, but probably wont buy till school is out. Hasn't sold his yet. Cld. Geo. Hartinger. Mother in law. Not ready to come yet."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/12/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Keas' Realtor in New Jersey Talked to closing officer. SHe said comm. letter was being sent today. Lease/option all together on Glenns + O'Neils Wrote Cheryl Goltz Jackson, Minnesota Talked to Mrs. Wayman on 6th St. house. Will list."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/13/1988">
			<text>"Rodney Wilson 636-6502 Jeff. tomorrow. Talked to Jackie Ayers. Hated to tell her the people didn't come back to lease hers. Talked to Karen Laramore - SHaron Bots. Cld on Wilsons."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/14/1988">
			<text>"Been over to see Lowell Campbell again. He said "Not today" for the listing. Cld. Tracey Cruts in Jackson Mo. 243-5676</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/15/1988">
			<text>"Talked to Mrs. Waymon again can get in Mon. 9:00 A.M. House inspection Voight/Clutch Informed me they had the inspection when the Voights dropped by Fri. Filling in for Sue + Shirley Not happy about the lack of communication."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/16/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/17/1988">
			<text>"Rec'd preliminary commitment letter on Neas Property. 2:15 - 2:30 Closing on Clutch/Voight. Phelps Co. Bank. Yes. Went well. Good surprise! 7% comm. instead of 6% Finally got keys to show Wayman property. Rodney wants to go at 5:30. Yuk! Hope to get an offer."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/18/1988">
			<text>"Everything stopped - call from Kevin at 7:40. Beth at hospital quite a day, quite an experience. We got Taylour Ahsley at 8:20. Hard labor for Beth."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/19/1988">
			<text>"Off work to help"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/20/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/21/1988">
			<text>"Off work to help the kids"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/22/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/23/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/24/1988">
			<text>"241-6586"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/25/1988">
			<text>"Back to work. List a property in Doolittle 1st thing. Go tomorrow to measure + set price. Talked to Rodney + Waymans Talked to Kelly Glenn - GOt that delivered to 20th"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/26/1988">
			<text>"444 394 Propane"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/27/1988">
			<text>"151"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/28/1988">
			<text>"Pick up warranty deed at United and W-9 Lois Cochran to see Scenic Dr. Stan Waskiewicz Cld. Will be her atr 9:00 to look at 4 Bdrm."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/29/1988">
			<text>"Gone to see Mother"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/30/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="10/31/1988">
			<text>"OFF today Gone to Hospital to see Mother"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/1/1988">
			<text>"Showed Marilyn's people"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/2/1988">
			<text>"11:30 Beauty Shop"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/3/1988">
			<text>"Got quotes on Ins. for Neas' 364 SMTS Last Mahoneys listing to C-21 Tried hard too Showed many times - Advertised to pieces. Showed it Tues. 3:00 P.M. Closign on Campbells. Cld. Elaine to see if she got all the info. She needed on Campbells. Call: Bill Beavers - Administrative Officer Called Phil Jones - To see if he could help w survey people coming in. Suggested calling Barb. Harris. I did. Couldn't give addresses but most are local people 120 coming next year."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/4/1988">
			<text>"Set closing for Neas 2:00 P.M. Chg'd to Mon. Tried to call Cheri Jorrison info from Titas 341-2066 Strawberry Patch 30 yr. fixed 10% 3% less than 50,000"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/5/1988">
			<text>"Showed Stan Waskowicz 7 homes. Liked Sycamore + Scenic best. Showed Donn Alexander Elsies. Starting to look like they may list here. Beth gone - Greg not coming James gone - trying to find Sherry Lost several listings sad!"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/6/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/7/1988">
			<text>"Closing NEas/Tate 2:00 Got closed w a prayer. On gas. Neas owes Talked renter into letting them store things."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/8/1988">
			<text>"Gone to Springfield."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/9/1988">
			<text>"Stan Waskiwicz Cld. Made offer by phone on Sycamore home."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/10/1988">
			<text>"Charley Johnson Babysit with Taylour Got call from Marvin Archuleta wants to see farms (cattle) Sat. at 10:00 Zuligs, Baileys, etc. Staying at Wayfarer Finally got Counter from Waymans of 9900. Cld Rodney - Willed Mom + decide Talked to Shirley Giesler about her listing wants Becky to call"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/11/1988">
			<text>"Kevin + James off. No counter on Salk home yet. Tried to call Stan. Cld. Cherri Jones - Gave info May start looking"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/12/1988">
			<text>"Out of town Becky's goign to show Mr. Archuleta for me w 50-50 split Helped her line out things and will help again. Greg will meet us for lunch Had good time, just possible at Dillards at 1:00 No didn't come."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/13/1988">
			<text>"Got deal together on Waskizwicz/Salk So happy! $22,190 away from million dollars. Keep going."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/14/1988">
			<text>"Need to call Alexanders - yes - good reception Lives in Green Acres."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/15/1988">
			<text>"Mld contracts to Stan Loveseat to be delivered today."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/16/1988">
			<text>"Mld application to Stan Waskiewicz"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/17/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/18/1988">
			<text>"9:00 To show: Perrys Mary Parry? tentative showing Call: Mike Marzuco 341-0928 Showed Stillmans, Bushongs Greenbriar tri-level, Hathaways Shady Oaks. Didn't show much emotion Biding her time, I guess. Call Donna Alexander to see about showing property Mon. P.M. Wants to see: 2 on Steeplechase + maybe Champs, maybe Mahoneys."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/19/1988">
			<text>"1:15 to show Alexander 2 on Steeplechase, Mahoneys + Champs cancelled"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/20/1988">
			<text>"Taylours Christening Nice! Snow! Snow! Snow! Great Grandparents couldn't come but Greg made it."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/21/1988">
			<text>"Day off - Gone to St. Louis"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/22/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/23/1988">
			<text>"Talked to Rodney Wilson. Still wants to make offer on Waymans but will wait for action of his"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/24/1988">
			<text>"Went smooth this year - Lots of fun"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/25/1988">
			<text>"Talked to Randy McCash about the people from Calif. Will maybe look tomorrow. I told him Sun. would be best."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/26/1988">
			<text>"Showed Stan Waskiewicz the Salk home they bought Seemed O.K. about it. Wants to close the 29th."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/27/1988">
			<text>"text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/28/1988">
			<text>"Talked to Pam and Mr. Heller - Finally got call from Mr. Heller saying they would accept the application. Closing scheduled for 29th. Talked to Randy McCash about lots of different farms. We will go look soon as I gather info and get lined out."</"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/29/1988">
			<text>"Talked to Randy again"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="11/30/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/1/1988">
			<text>"Look at a farm today - 3:30 P.M. Meet Ken Johson to see acreage near Pilot Knob"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/2/1988">
			<text>"Look at P Hwy farm with Gerald Pietsch.Appmt. with Ken Johnson Chg'd to today."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/3/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/4/1988">
			<text>"All day w concerts"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/5/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/6/1988">
			<text>"Showed: Randy a farm so of St. James. Was really excited about it. Will call his investor tonight. Greg cld. Coming down Fri eve. Will decorate our tree at midnight."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/7/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Stan Waskiewicz. Has mld. verifications will try to close the 29th."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/8/1988">
			<text>"Jills b- day Celebration in order - 7:30 Fun"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/9/1988">
			<text>"Greg coming. Would like to go shopping w Sherry on desk at 2:30 Sharon Jones Arrived un announced. Looking for rental. SHowed duplex $250 CC Hwy. Very int. in Longs for renting 6 mo. then purchase. Sharon 308 W. Grand - Sedalia 65301 (816) 826-6793."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/10/1988">
			<text>"Mr. Lannings b-day Going Xmas shopping w Greg + hopefully Beth Party at McCash's Ready to go back to see home in St. James and ready to see farm at P Hwy. + the big one."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/11/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/12/1988">
			<text>"Called Ellis Copeland - Will get back on appmt. Called Marcia Babysite w Taylour."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/13/1988">
			<text>"Checked w Pam at Capital. Will send in everything today on Waskiewicz. SHould get call an approval tomorrow. Contacted Jonnita for abstract. 341-0920 Randy McCash"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/14/1988">
			<text>""</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/15/1988">
			<text>"9:30 Sharon Jones int. in Longs To see Myers farm w Mary 2:00 Need to send maps to Mr. O'Neal and get Randy to see it. Luncheon w Lanning bunch 12:00 Call: Mr. Heller about approval on Waskiewicz this P.M. Yes, it was approved."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/16/1988">
			<text>"Lunch w James 7:00 P.M. Zenos - Office husband/wife party good time. 8:30 A.M. "</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/17/1988">
			<text>"Enjoyed shopping w Beth Babysite w Taylour Stan Wask. cld.; ruined my weekend. He asked to withdraw offer. Advised him that it was too late. We had contract now with loan approval. Asked me to "</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/18/1988">
			<text>"Johnita Cld seller. Will not release buyer. Too late, they said."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/19/1988">
			<text>"Advised Stan of sellers refusal to release. 5:30 - My house - office party gift exchange. Carol Wask. cld. during party to ask for copy of contract."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/20/1988">
			<text>"Suppose to show St. James farm again to take pictures ot send Mr. O'Neal. Logan got sick - can't go today"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/21/1988">
			<text>"To show: Randy McCash at 4:00 (The Bell Farm) tot ake pictures to send Mr. O'Neal."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/22/1988">
			<text>"Got call from Shirley. Has prospect in 100,000 range. Sent pictures of lots of homes. GO to Sherrys at 12:30. My folks coming today after 3:00. Had a good time last night, soaking in Christmas; baking cookies Bake cookies tonight Ate out w my folks. Beth + Kevin + Taylour. Made 2 apple pies, rice stuffing + strawberry roll. Need to decide about pre-closing inspection on Salk property."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/23/1988">
			<text>"Barb on P.M. Picked up aerial photo on Bell farm to make to O'Neal Talked to Shirley again + sent more listings. Greg coming around 11:00. So thankful he gets Sat and most of Sun off. All of us eating pizza out tonight. Greg coming tonight. Make egg casserole and fix him a steak."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/24/1988">
			<text>"Bake ham roast - Greg hair appmt 11:30 Christmas at home this year for my 1st time in all 52 years. Hope we can make it very very special. Getting anxious! Xmas Eve at Sherrys Need to make Egg casserole. We made a great effort. It was good for so many!"</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/25/1988">
			<text>"James folks coming for breakfast. Put turkey roast on."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/26/1988">
			<text>"Off today."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/27/1988">
			<text>"Open Keep in touch w Shirley Day 364-5569 Stay on top farm deal w Randy Start bldg. for '89. Talked to Marcia McCash on farm deal. Talked to Gene Hartling's wife. Going to leave Rolla. Will list w Becky + I since they are friends of hers too now. Will call me after the 8th."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/28/1988">
			<text>"Barb/Becky Shared Shirley Day. Doesn't know at this point if her kids will rent or buy. Sue cld. Stan. Does not plan to come for closing. Will I ever learn not to count on them till closing?? Flaky people pursueing employment in Ohio after putting a contract on home in Rolla. Start again! Make some money quick. Got Lyle Cmaps listing extended."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/29/1988">
			<text>"Cld. Cheri Jones - NOt ready sounds like Call Greg Cld. George Holland - Not int. in re-listing now Waskiewicz Closing set for today? Backed out. Not coming. Got some more homes ready in little lower price range for Shirley Day. Look for a better day! Cld. Ladonna Simmons about Wilson reduction. Can't do anything new Cld. Mike + Mld. back to Mike Marzuco HCR 32 - Box 236. Tried to call Kathy Franklin Cld. Randy Wed. Soon as they get tapes, they'll fly out and take a look."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/30/1988">
			<text>"Talked ot Tom Laramore. Karen might want to see home on 2 mi. rd. Town and Country. Told him about Stillmons. 2:00 P.M. Show Shirley Day Briarwood Condo. Check w Dorothy Gilmore 1st. Barbara Wilson Cld. Inquiring of the Water Slide Got info. Will call back (573) 364-1706. (312) 571-5069. $175,000."</text>
		</entry>

		<entry date="12/31/1988">
			<text>"Wrote Corrottos Rt. 2 F. Bay Hope Greg comes back down. Not going to but we may go up or meet him halfway Sun."</text>
		</entry>





	</entries>